#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/vaibhavsisinty (LinkedIn) www.sisinty.com (Personal)

## Top Skills

Growth Hacking Marketing Strategy Entrepreneurship

# Languages

English (Professional Working)
Hindi (Professional Working)
Telugu (Native or Bilingual)

#### Honors-Awards

SAM Global Youth Award Fast Emerging Digital Media Startup of the Year

# Vaibhav Sisinty

Head of Marketing, Klook India & ME | Ex-Uber | Growth Hacker | Speaker

Mumbai

# Summary

Hi, I'm Vaibhav, a growth hacker by profession and an entrepreneur from heart.

Ever since my childhood (literally, I was 8 years old), I began doing marketing. Back then, I applied some spectacular marketing techniques to sell Beyblades at 200% of its cost price.

However, I fell in love with marketing much later when I started "Discovery Android" in 2011. I, along with 3 team members, was successful in growing it to 1M+ page views in a year's time. After Google banned our Adsense account (a story for another day), we had to shut down the website.

However, failures didn't stop me from experimenting and trying new things.

So, in the second year of engineering in 2013, when students are generally busy studying new subjects, I started CrazyHeads, where I was managing a team of 14 crazy heads who had a knack for growth marketing.

In less than 3 years, we served over 100 clients from India, US, Brazil, Australia etc. In 2014, CrazyHeads won "Fast Emerging Digital Media Startup of the Year" award.

In 2015, I decided to exit from CrazyHeads and take on the next challenge.

Uber, the \$40B beast now, was then trying to get its foot placed in Indian Market. I joined Uber to help them tap the unexplored markets in India and increase brand visibility. At the age of 23, I was promoted to the post of Marketing Manager.

From merely 100 trips per week, we scaled up the market to reach a million trips every week by applying a well-planned and executed growth strategy.

Since then, I have been a marketing consultant to over 60 startups, helping them to find new customers & grow exponentially through growth hacking at half the budget of digital marketing.

Till now, I have launched three courses on Growth Hacking -Linkedin, FB Chatbots and Instagram (Visit sisinty.com to check them out).

Entrepreneur, KillerStartups, BuzzFeed, The Hindu and other reputed publications have featured me in their articles and other resources.

I have delivered over 40 workshops and 20 talks in top companies, colleges as well as online events. Get a glimpse of a few of my talks here (https://sisinty.com/speaking/)

If you want to talk more about growth hacking, marketing strategy or especially Linkedin (since it's my personal favourite), hit me up or just email me: vaibhav@sisinty.com

# Experience

Klook Head Of Marketing, India & ME October 2019 - Present (11 months) Mumbai Area, India

- Leading the marketing for Klook India and Middle East, including brand, customer acquisition, user engagement and the resulting financial performance.
- Leading the channel managers who're handling campaigns, social media, partnerships, design, performance, affiliates and PR (I might have a couple of roles for you Check out Klook Career page)
- Building the brand Klook as a synonym to international travel for Indians (creating a full-fledged experience which goes beyond booking flights or hotel)

#### About Klook:

Think international travel, think Klook – we're on a mission to revolutionise how you experience a foreign trip.

Klook is the world's largest travel activities and services booking platform. With 30+ global offices and 3,000+ employees all over the world, Klook gives an unforgettable experience to international travellers through 100,000+ activities in over 350 cities.

With more than \$500 M funding from marquee investors like Softbank, Matrix Partners, Goldman Sachs etc, Klook is proud of being the most funded organisation in tours and activities sector globally.

Found a role that interests you? Hit me up with the link to the role :)

Sisinty.com
Chief Growth Hacker
September 2015 - Present (5 years)

- Helping startups scale-up and tap the new markets using growth hacking,
- Delivering talks, workshops & seminars in colleges, universities, online & offline summits and other events on growth hacking, marketing strategies and entrepreneurship,
- Teaching online courses on growth hacking (Launched three courses till now Facebook, Linkedin & Instagram)
- Acted as a marketing consultant to startups like Speque, OpenPizza, Linq Stores, FarEye, Eruvaka, ResearchWire, LinkAllData etc.,
- Generated revenue of USD 7.9K with a 2-member team (including me) using AdSense and native ads. Used growth marketing strategy to make 16 posts viral (5000+ shares per post on all social media platforms) within 4 months of execution.
- Helped dropshipping sites to drive sales of INR 2M+ by selling beauty products, gadgets etc using viral video ads, remarketing and unique cart abandonment techniques on Shopify and Woo Commerce stores,
- Assisted startups to fetch maximum ROI out of influencer marketing using tools like skreem.io, influencer.in etc.

upGrad.com
Guest Lecturer / Mentor
September 2019 - Present (1 year)

- upGrad enables the aspirants to acquire various skills through online courses and education programs from top universities.
- Some of the academic partners involve University of Cambridge, Duke, MICA, NMIMS, Liverpool John Moores University etc.
- I am associated with upGrad as a guest lecturer, delivering sessions on growth marketing and entrepreneurship.
- I also mentor the learners through the sharing of practical case studies and real-life experiences.

#### Uber

4 years 1 month

Growth Strategy - Latin America August 2018 - September 2019 (1 year 2 months) Mexico City Area, Mexico

Catering to Mexico, Brazil, Peru, Chile, Colombia, Argentina.

#### Marketing Manager

March 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 6 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

- Have ideated and executed several Digital and Brand campaigns like, "Month Of Magic", "Uber undi kada", "The Uber Marketing" etc.
- Worked with the BD team to sign MOU's with GMR Airport and HMRL. Spearheaded operations for Uber at high value places like: Airports, Metros, Railways, Malls etc.
- Ran multiple successful experiments both on rider and driver side to improve metrics like C/R, PUDO etc. at Airports and Metros.
- One of the partnerships lead for the country. Have cracked barter deals of over 5CR INR with brands like Airtel, Vodafone, BigBasket, Audi, Rentomojo, Driven etc.
- Lead rider engagement, retention and various CRM campaigns.
- Handled launch and execution of uberCENTRAL, a B2C product. Lead a team of 6 associates cracking over 70 clients in the region.
- Launched HIRE, Premier, Moto, Auto. Handled efforts from product growth to engagement for the region.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams including operations, legal, policy, PR, engineering to generate demand & retain existing users and for policy partnerships like GES.

Launch - Marketing Coordinator February 2016 - February 2017 (1 year 1 month)

Vishakhapatnam Area, India

- Managed FB app-install campaigns, rider engagement & retention campaigns for launch cities like Vizag, Indore, Mangalore, Bhubaneswar etc. Was able to get the cost of install down to 0.60\$. Also ran search and YouTube campaigns for Brand awareness.
- Was in charge of all ATL & BTL activities including media buying and ROI analysis with budgets of over 3CR INR annually. Achieved lowest offline rider acquisition cost in the country.
- Owned Rider Life Cycle Management for Vizag rider base attaining low rider churn rate and higher trips per rider while increasing the average fare.
- Conceptualized & executed end-to-end marketing campaigns uberLIVE, uberHEALTH, uberDHOL, uberDIWALI, uberMATCH, uberMOVIE etc.
- Spearheaded all the rider communications Emails, SMS, App popups, Social.

# Launch Coordinator September 2015 - January 2016 (5 months)

Visakhapatnam

- Co-Launched operations in Vizag. Scaled Vizag from scratch to a 30M\$
   Business.
- Spearheaded the end-to-end operations for Vizag on both sides of the business Driver Operations and Rider Operations.
- Formulated rider & driver strategy acquiring 1000s of drivers and scaling the rider base to over 200k riders at optimal.

### LearnApp

Mentor

November 2018 - August 2019 (10 months)

India

- LearnApp provides affordable, high-quality financial education through online courses taught by veterans.
- People like R. Gopalakrishnan (Executive Director, Tata Sons), Ashish Kashyap (Founder of Goibibo, RedBus and Payu), Nitin Kamath (CEO Zerodha) have been teaching online courses on various topics on LearnApp.
- I have taught FB Messenger Chatbot Marketing on LearnApp, enabling the marketers to use FB Messenger bot to run marketing campaigns and acquire new customers.

CrazyHead Solutions
Founder & Chief Growth Hacker
June 2013 - July 2015 (2 years 2 months)

Vishakhapatnam Area, India

- Raised a seed funding of INR 2M for the digital media startup pertaining to need of the clients across PR & digital marketing domain;
- Worked with more than 20 brands and over 100 clients in 15 months of projections;
- Conducted 30+ workshops on Digital Marketing, Ethical Hacking, Design Thinking etc.

#### Jagriti Yatra

Yatri

December 2013 - January 2014 (2 months)

Was part of leap, Building India through Enterprise.

Travelled to 11 different places in India meeting the sucessful personalities and social entrepreneurs, trying to understand the model and analyse it..

Jagriti Yatra is an annual train journey that takes 375 highly motivated students on an empowering journey circumnavigating India. The 'Yatris' meet Role models across 12 destinations spread across the country. Role models are people who have stepped out of their comfort zones in order to achieve something.

#### Discovering Android

Cofounder

November 2011 - December 2012 (1 year 2 months)

Visakhapatnam

- Started a blog on Android back in 2011 (I was 19 years old) was able to drive traffic of over 120k page views per month at its peak.
- Used AdSense and sponsored posts( eventually got banned in 3 months due to android rooting content ) to generate a revenue of over 400USD for 3 months.
- Used on page SEO and basic backlinking methods which used to work back in 2011 like commenting on blogs, backlink exchanges, guest posting, PBN's etc.

# Education

Internet